Thank you for watching!
Almighty Presents Deliver! Fun Salmon Season 4
Secure Future Food for Japan! Food Crisis Part 2
Deliver! Fun Farm Season 4
Last time, you started the second workshop and learned about food equipment!
And then, we tried a team fast-paced quiz!
If you can collect two of each of these five food cards, you win!
Now, as you can see the stockpile status of each team, or each country
If the Republic of Blue Republic can stockpile 2 more cards, they will win!
What will happen in the second half of the game?
July 2021 release: Tie-up song with tradition
In the music video for "Umaimono Fan Club
In the music video for the "Good Food Fan Club", what is it that the brother is eating?
What is it? What was it? What was it?
Oh, yes, I know what it is.
Thank you.
What was it?
I think it might help you remember.
I'll give you a hint.
It's a different color.
A slightly different color?
Different.
Funny.
No!
What was that?
I'll make a gesture.
That one?
Oh, it's a gesture I can see.
Did you see it?
Did you see it?Did you see that?
Open your mouth wide.
Sukiyaki.
No, sir!
What was it?
One more time, one more list, please.
Oh, chopsticks?
Oh, that's welcome back, too.
Yes, chopsticks.
Chopsticks?
Seven of the best.
Maximum first class seven.
Not because of this.
Oh, okay.
Okay, I'll show you what it is.
This one?
Not even close.
What?
But it's like that.
It's kind of heavy.
What color?
Here we go.
Shoes!
Yes, shoes.
I'll just have to let you answer that.
I'm going to have to let you answer that one.
Four letters.
Yes, sir.Yes, sir.
Carrots?
What's the answer?
This one!
What's the correct answer?
The correct answer is pumpkin!
The correct answer is a pumpkin!
Here's the music video
Good Food Fan Club
Pumpkin is our favorite food, right?
You look really happy!
So, National Food Crisis!
We've done it!
Another National Food Crisis!
Kanda Kingdom suffered a major natural disaster
Combi and Yuika are losing producers
The Republic of Green is experiencing exchange rate fluctuations
Infectious disease outbreak in the Land of Food Lovers
Penalties are as you can see
Question 12
Released in January 2020
Tie-in song with Almighty
Resonate! In the music video for Fampare!
What is Motono Honey eating?
Don't eat it!
Hibike FANPARAE
I'll release it one more time
I'll release you one more time
It's a quick press!It's a fast push.
It's a quick push.
Here we go.
Black tea?
Correct!
I did it again.
I eat kabocha every time.
Do you eat kabocha every time?
This is the music video "Sound the Fanfare".
Mr. Matoba looks like he's eating well.
We can only import it.
From here.
From here?
They put vegetables in it.
Wow! We're reaching, aren't we?
Yes!
Vegetables imported from the Awa-o Republic!
We're in! Can we get away with this?
Question 13
Kanji character "dojo
Diffusion is going!
Correct!
Excellent!
Is this a math meeting?
We have to go in, we have to go in.
Incoming players, please.
Finally, we're back.
I always thought that the countries that love to eat would be eaten by the incoming goods.
That's what I think.That's what I think.
Yes, sir.
There's a lot of history here.
The country that loves to eat, led by Moe-chan, has returned with an entrance card.
And now, to the Republic of Blue, the country with the incorrect answer...
Conflict, normal instability, and food crisis card of terrorism.
The next time you get a correct answer, you will not be able to choose imports!
Next, question 14.
Next up.
Where is Yuna Kanda from?
What? Is that it?
It's already down.
No, it's not!
Yuna Kanda is from Chiba Prefecture.
Chiba Prefecture produces the most.
How do you write "ochisei" in kanji?
What? It's so easy!
Let's see... fall, flower, live.
Correct!
Excellent!
Now, let's move on to the site with the imports!
Vegetables are back in the Republic of Greenery!
A big blow to the duo and the yuika team, who were reaching for it!
Now, to the 15th question!
Stay tuned for the next installment!
Not fossil resources such as oil and coal,
as long as there is sun, water, and plants
called "00 fuel".
What is this 00?
Renewable electricity?Renewable Power?
No, sir!
Oh, I see.
Correct!
Do you import meat?
Yes, we do.
Import meat from the Republic of AoAo, a country that loves to eat!
Moe-chan, who hates to lose, is going to take the bait!
Next
Question
How many have you had now?
Wow, how many is this?
Sixteen.
Correct!
That's great!
Once we imported dairy products and got them back, now we're going to produce them. Can we get closer to victory?
Question 17
Present Present! What is the name of the comedy duo that joined as hosts of Fun Farm Season 3?
Osenso Marumaru Konomoto!
Kyoda-san
Correct answer!
Congratulations!
You have a good delivery.
I'm relieved.
Yes, sir.
Tsurumi.
Amazing.
I love the shaking.
Amazing.Oh, my God.
From her.
Dairy.
Oh, my God.
I don't care what you do for a living.
I think we did it.
The first correct answer in 17 questions... Kanda Kingdom!
The first move was to import dairy products, which should not be taken from that Tsurumi team!
Tension is growing between the two countries.
Question 18
More than 90% water and it has the effect of opening from the body side
Eggplant
It is a type of polyphenol that has an oxidizing effect and is said to be useful in preventing lifestyle-related diseases
The pigment of the skin is
Skin pigment
Eggplant
Correct answer
It is amazing!
Vegetables
Vegetable
The duo and Yuika get vegetables and reach again!
Question 19
Which prefecture has the largest number of members who live in Yokohama, where all the water lines are drawn, and which prefecture has the largest number of members who live in Yokohama, where all the water lines are drawn and where all the water lines are drawn?
There is a difference!
Saitama and Tokyo.
Correct!
That's a lot of Tokyo.
That's right.That's right.
Saitama and Tokyo have 3 each.
Heh.
That's right.
So, blue, yellow and red.
Let's start the second round!
Incoming!
Blue, please listen to me properly.
Oh, no, the Republic of Blue imported the incoming goods from the duo and Yuka!
And what a duo and yuika who have caught an epidemic of infectious disease!
Penalty is off for a while
But in fact, the next problem is the final problem, so the food crisis is averted!
And finally, we had a leader's duel.
The current card stockpile is as follows
Due to the heated competition, the rules were suddenly changed, and the team with the most cards after the last problem was the winner!
Is Kanda Kingdom in trouble at this point?
But you can help someone else win!
Who will win?
Question 20
Fukuno presents Delivering Handsome Season 4
Who is the big winner of the first episode?
Oh!
That was some made-up endurance and endurance.
Oh, maybe that's similar.
No!
The man from the future has arrived.
Nice try!
The man from the future.The Futurist.
It was a close call.
Karin's.
I would like to think that all participants
in finding out about PMS.
I think it's a mistake.
Is that okay?
Yes, if that's what you mean.
He's saying something.
Well, what do you want me to do?
I don't know if it's right.
I'm thinking of a future specific device.
No, sir!
Let's see.
Oh, no.
To the future ex-baca!
LOL!
No, it's not.
(laughs)
So, um...
The correct answer is that attachment came from the future
Ahhh...
I hear that.
Like food security.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What's the title of the food security guarantee?
I hear that.
What the hell is that, Nanako Ota?
Yes, sir.
Now, at the end, the duo is tied, and the winning team will be decided by a game of rock-paper-scissors-scissors between Yuka and the Republic of AoYo.Now, the last game of the tournament will be a rock-paper-scissors-scissors match between the tied duo, YUICA and the Republic of Blue to decide the winning team.
Let's play rock, paper, scissors!
Rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors!
It's going to be a hot one!
Let's go with the icons!
Icon!
Yeah!
That's great!
Thanks for watching to the end!
Coami's Meat Box!
Deliver! First time in a fan farm and first time winner! Congrats to the duo and Yuka!
I got to watch the whole thing and feel the history of the country.
It's like taking back what was taken from you.
But then, towards the end of the show...
I felt like we should try harder to produce more.
It was so beautiful to see that kind of spirit growing in everyone.
It was very beautiful.
Let's go in peace.
It really made me think about it because I saw the diagram of the lodge.
Really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really
Really, really, really, really, really, really
It made me think.
Of course we'll take care of you
It was a wonderful experience!
So that's it!
I was prepared for the creamed food chicken!
It's been an epic battle.
But today... we are going to have a workshop.Today, we're going to have a workshop.
Since everyone has been collecting
I'm going to give you another shot at it.
In Season 4, we're going to learn about a lot of different things related to food survey takers.
We're going to learn a lot of things related to the food survey, and we're going to think about
We're going to be looking at the theme of "Choosing Japanese Food".
We're going to choose domestic products.
Today, I'd like to ask you to come up with a YouTube project that will make you want to choose domestic food.
I'd like to ask you to think about a YouTube project that will make you want to choose domestic products.
Let's call it
A YouTube presentation competition that will make you want to choose Japanese products.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I'm going to ask you all to come up with a YouTube project.
That's right.
The information for the project is
It is a project to be made by all of you
This is what it means.
Two teams
This time, you will be divided into the Tsurumi team and
Yamato team and Tsurumi team.
and Yamato team to come up with a plan.
As for the evolution method...
The producer this time will be Mr. Kyoto.
Mr. Kyoto will be judging and deciding.
Evolution at its best!
That's great!
The point of evolution is the presentation.
I'm telling the contents of the project.
I would like to start with the title of the project
And then the content of the planAnd planning details
How to spread the word
Points to be particular about
We would like you to summarize these four points in a clip
I would like you to make a presentation.
I am also making a clip.
That's why...
Um...
The first one.
Two teams will receive
Finally, J3 gift wrapping!
Yay!
I'm sure you were right about this one, too, right?
That's right!
Ladies and Gentlemen!
I'd like to present this to all the kids' fans.
I'd like to make a presentation.
Mr. Haru.
That's right.
Finally.
As if it wasn't.
I'm going to leave it completely up to you.
And since you're going to do this.
I'll think of something.
Well...
After the heated discussion between Nidicon and the participants
What kind of project will be born after the heated discussion between Nidicon and the participants?
While everyone is working on their ideas
I heard that that person also came up with a plan.
Everyone who is watching this videoYou're watching this video, and so are you.
YouTube project that makes you want to choose domestic products.
If you have any good ideas
Please let us know in the comments section.
Let us know!
Let's see what you can come up with!
I asked you to play a game like this. Did you get it?
Yes, it's OK!
Excellent!
You know... while we were discussing this.
While you were discussing, Kyota came up with an example all by himself.
Amazing!
I guess it's important to set a good example for the judges.
For us.
It raises the bar.
It's not a model, it's an idea.
A model.
Now, please give us your presentation.
I've got one of these, too.
Please go along with me as if you were rehearsing for the camera.
Here is the presentation I came up with.
Project title: I tried to be a producer's pop-up.
Thank you very much.
I focused on the point of making people want to choose the pop-up shop.
I focused on this pop-up in the supermarket.
The pop-ups in supermarkets have pictures of the producers' faces on them.
I often choose pop-up shops based on those pictures.
I was wondering if it would be a good idea for us to go there and be a part of it.
The contents of this project are as follows
I'd like to have my face on the pop-ups of more than 6 times as many producers.Having your face on a pop-up of a producer that is six times larger than your own...
It's nice to have your face on a pop-up!
And this one probably has Nember, Nijikon Nember, etc. in it.
If it's a pumpkin made by Karin...
I think people will want to go out and buy it.
Of course, I'm going to help with the production.
But I think that the people who came today would be especially interested in seeing the pop-ups.
I'm sure that everyone will know how the pop-ups look like.
I also have the ulterior motive that everyone will know about it.
That's the most important point.
The most important point is to see the producer's face.
I chose Pop because I could really see the producer's face
I chose the pops based on the producer's face and comments.
As a result of looking at myself in a different way, I came up with this project.
I came up with this plan.
What do you think?
Amazing!
It's really good!
Wow!
You thought of it all by yourself.
Thank you.
Yes, like this.
Yes, here is the project we came up with!
Seino
Nijikon Lover Man and I are going to make
Nationwide good food pukke!
Looks so good!
You know what we did?
When it comes to choosing domestic food...When it comes to choosing domestic products
I don't know, rice or something.
I did a library list the other day.
What kind of rice is there and where is it?
and what kind of taste it has
I think I know what kind of rice there is and what it tastes like.
I don't know about other ingredients.
I thought it's hard to know about other ingredients.
Basically, I can tell you what ingredients are famous
and how delicious they are.
I don't know what ingredients are famous and how they taste.
I think it's difficult to choose ingredients with that in mind.
I think it might be difficult to make choices with that in mind.
I would like to have something that allows me to know
I personally wanted something that would help me to know
That's why I decided to create this project.
The contents are as follows
I love you man! I'm sure he's in every corner of the country.
I'd like to ask him to recommend ingredients from each area.
(It's too much work to list all the ingredients, so I've asked him to recommend meats and vegetables in particular.
I'm looking for recommendations for meats, vegetables, etc.
I'll narrow it down to a few and ask for your recommendations.
So, from all over the country.
We have this cabbage that's delicious.
No, we have delicious cabbage here, too.
We have a lot of such ingredients from all over the world.
And we all try them together.
"Oh, this cabbage is sweet.
This cabbage is sweet, or this cabbage is crunchy.
We all tasted these things together.We'll eat something like that together.
We will make a distribution list of each foodstuff.
And then we'll make a distribution chart.
It would be nice if you could teach us how to eat them.
We're also going to learn how to eat eggplant.
A big round eggplant tastes good when it's roasted like this.
There are various ways to eat eggplant.
If we could find a way to eat them
If we can find it together, we will find it.
We will make it into a database.
I would like to make a database and compile it into a book.
I'd like to make a book.
And this is it.
It's almost always covered.
The way to spread it is
First of all, I'd like to solicit
I'm going to start by soliciting various things from all of the LOVEMAN.
And then we have one connection with our favorite people.
And then we publish the database in a booklet.
And then we publish it in a booklet.
Of course, people who watch the program can find out about it
But in order to deliver it to people who don't know about it
We're going to run a tweet campaign
We're going to give it away as a gift.
You know Zenro's vegetable book?
Maybe you could make it into a campaign like you did with that one.
I'm a bit of a geek here.
If you sell something like that at Natsukomi...
When you publish something specialized...
It becomes a big topic of conversation.It's a big topic of conversation, isn't it?
That's when it's really useful.
Like, "What's this?
I thought it would be fun to do something like that.
There are two ways to spread the word.
I thought of two ways to spread the word.
The main point is that
I really wanted to do this, so I came up with this idea.
I think it would be a grand project if we could do it.
All the people in the world will want a permanent copy.
Maybe even the people of the world would want it.
I think it would be a database that people all over the world would want to have.
The first call and the last one.
I'd like to distribute it, and I'd like to put it out to the world.
and the final stage of spreading the word.
I think the point is that there are two levels of spreading
I think that's the point.
That's amazing.
I'm going to go in that short time.
So far...
You did it with great rhythm, didn't you?
Yes, sir.
That's great.
Let's see what you've got.
We've come up with a plan.
Let's do it.
Let's build a two-hour clothesline.
The purpose of this project is to build a rainbow corn field, where we can grow vegetables together with our viewers.
The purpose of this project is to grow our own homegrown products. We will build a rainbow corn farm and sell the produce directly to the public.
But it might be difficult to build a house from scratch, so we're going to build a direct sales place for the rainbow corn that we've been selling.Well, it might be difficult to build a house from the ground up, so we're going to have a rainbow corn corner at the direct sales places we've been to.
So, we'd like to have a rainbow corn corner at the direct sales places we've been to, and have the vegetables grown by rainbow corn there.
We'd like to have a rainbow corn corner at the direct sales places we've been to, so that people can come directly to the direct sales places with goods and stickers that only those who go to the direct sales places can get.
And the way to spread the word is to use the hashtag "rainbow corn market", and it's hard to make an idol market.
I don't think people will see it at all.
And we can show how we make it on tiktok or something, and we can do a commercial for it.
We're aiming for young people.
We're also aiming at young people. We want to let young people know that it's fun to make things by themselves.
The main points of this event are that you can eat the food we made, and you can work hard together.
And we can get rainbow cone goods. And anyway, we can make it together as cooperative partners.
As a cooperative partner, you can make all the rainbow cones with the tie-up software of the cert.
The point is that we can make rainbow cones together.
Applause.
That's very interesting.
Both of them were really good.
They're great.
I think we can do it.
It could be a real dikake.
This one was also judged by producer Kyota.
It was a showdown, wasn't it?
Both are very good, but you have to decide, don't you?
I don't have any authority.
I've been asked to be the producer.
It's not that it's difficult, it's just that you both have great presentation skills.
And of course, both of you are great.
And the content of the project...
both of them are great, but
But when you think about the scale of Almighty
the idea of creating a nationwide projectThe idea of creating a buzz around the country
can't be realized anywhere else.
I think it's a unique point of this channel
I think it's a unique point of this channel.
So, one hand, this one
Using TikTok
This is a project that utilizes the power of rainbow corn
on the other hand, this one is a project that utilizes the power of the rainbow cone.
The contents of both projects are interesting and
and they are both highly diffuse.
It's really hard to find the right course.
It's very difficult.
I'm torn.
Can we forget about the cruza pop-up?
That's the thing.
And in answer to my question.
I could be part of this side.
My impression is...
Blue, I'm on the Juana team.
So that's one vote.
I see.
The result.
It was Ao-chan and Juana's team.
What a surprise... the winner of the YouTube presentation was
Ao and Juana's "Let's build a rainbow corn farm!
So, the winning team will receive
All of you!
We're all in the finals!
Thank you.
If Ao's team comes up with a plan later...If you do a project for the blue team even later.
It would be nice to have more than one vote.
Absolutely.
I'll be working very hard.
You should tell me if they do it.
It was wonderful!
That was the YouTube project presentation showdown that made me want to choose a domestic product.
Finally, I'd like everyone to think about something.
In order to utilize food stably
I would like to think about what we should do to ensure the stable use of food.
I would like to think about what we should do in order to utilize food stably.
I'd like to give you a hint.
It's connected to the quiz we did today.
What did you all think about? I think it is also related to the question
What do you think?
What do you think? What do you think?
I don't really feel that we are in a food crisis at all.
but I think we should not take it for granted that we can eat plenty of food now.
Don't take it for granted
Don't take it for granted that you can eat all the food you have right now.
Don't take it for granted that you have plenty of food right now.
I want to take care to stay healthy, even if it's just for a short while.
I want to take care to stay healthy, not only for myself but also for the people around me, and also in areas that may affect the crops,
I hope I can do things like not leaving garbage behind or something like that.
I was surprised when I took this quiz, "Prepare for a Food Crisis.
I was surprised at the number of factors that can cause a food crisis.
I was surprised at the number of factors that can cause a food crisis, even if it is only in our own country.
It is amazing how many factors can cause a food crisis in your own country.
I realized how important it is to have a stable food supply in your own country.
I felt that it is very important to choose domestically produced food first and foremost, so that the culture of food in Japan can be further developed.I think it is important to value the culture of domestically produced food in Japan, and I think it is important for Japanese people to know more about it.
I think it's important that we value the culture of food in Japan, and I think it's important that the people of Japan know more about it.
[Applause] I feel that it is easy to imagine what we can do in Japan.
It seems to me that it is easy to imagine what you can do in Japan,
I think it is important for Japanese people to know more about the culture of cultural food in Japan.
I hope that workshops like this one and this video will help people learn more about Japan.
I would be very happy if you could take an interest in one thing today for the future of Japan.
Lastly, I would like to ask for your brief comments.
Please do so.
Well, I was able to get to know the members of Nijikon.
Please ask me who to ask.
Who is asking me? I'm sorry.
Yes, I was able to get in touch with Nidicon members after all.
It was the same thing. It just happened.
I'm sorry, we just happened to be together.
Thank you very much for the workshop.
I think it is important to have a good balance when it comes to food.
I was in a game, so I had to take pictures from that side.
As you mentioned, it is also important to increase production.
As you mentioned, I hope to create a kind world where everyone can win and everyone can be happy.
I hope that we can create such a friendly world where everyone can win and everyone can be happy.
I had a lot of fun talking with you and playing games with you. Thank you very much.
I was so surprised.
I mean, you were pretty close to me, right?
It was quite a surprise, wasn't it?
Thank you very much for this precious opportunity.
Yes, it was something,
I work in the education field, so I enjoy playing games like this with children,
I also like quizzes and study,
I like quizzes and studying with children, and I have made some new discoveries, such as that this could be the cause of the appetite period,Among them, I found new discoveries like this could be the cause of the appetite period,
I hope that I can help children learn about these things and expand their world,
I hope that I can help them expand their world.
Thank you for your hard work.
It was fun, wasn't it?
I hope you enjoy watching the fun videos.
Please do it by all means.
I look forward to working with you all.
Thank you very much.
That concludes the Sod That! Fun Farm Season 4 Workshop #2, Food Listening, is over.
Thank you all very much for your time today.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry I had to join you shortly after I delivered this.
When people talk about the food crisis, it's a little bit...
It was a little bit difficult for me to know about the food crisis.
It was difficult to find an opportunity to get involved.
but through the game, I had a lot of fun with the participants.
I was able to laugh and have fun while
I had a lot of fun and learned a lot of information
It was a lot of fun!
I'm so glad.
That was great!
You got a lot of prizes, didn't you, Mori?
Oh, no.
I said it was because I liked it.
They all took it away from me.
No, no, no, no.
It's hard, isn't it?
It's great that you're participating for the first time.
Even I can't get Moe's prize.Even I can't get Moe's prize.
LOL!
You're right.
My leg muscles were putting pressure on it.
You said it well.
Yeah.
Oh, no.
Nice work.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I hate it when things you love disappear from your own country.
I'd hate to lose something I love from my country.
That's true.
Why?
It's bad, isn't it?
There's a huge food crisis in my country.
Laughs.
We're in a situation where we can't get food.
I felt it firsthand.
I thought, "This is not good.
We were in a food crisis.
And when we got infected and we got ourselves infected
We're going to have to stop.
You know what I mean?
That's what the fans were saying.
I'm just trying to stay healthy.
I realized that again.
Yes, that's right.
And that's what we're trying to do.
And now that we've realized it.
I want everyone to know about it.I want everyone to know about it.
I'd like you all to know...
I'm familiar with many of them.
It all started with the food crisis.
The food crisis.
Yes.
But the most important thing is to know.
Is the most important thing.
The most important thing is to know.
That's for sure.
Before taking any action
It is important to know first
Like in this case.
Whether it's a game or YouTube
I'd like to continue to have fun and let people know
I want to continue to do so.
Yes, sir.
Yes, ma'am.
By the way, Moe.
How's the food crisis in your stomach?
You know...
I don't think it's good to fight.
Let's eat together in peace.
That's right.
Shall we cut up the peaches?
Yeah, let's.
Laughs.
See you next time.
So, how was everyone?How did you all do?
I hope you were able to learn about the difficult topic of food crises in an easy-to-understand way through the game.
There are many factors that contribute to food crises, and some of them could happen at any time.
We should not forget to be thankful for the food we have in our daily life and spend our time every day.
So, please look forward to the next issue!